Claudia de Lima

Denver, CO 80203 * (303)503-8883 * ac.delima13@gmail.com

ABOUT ME

After working in restaurant management for the past 7+ years, I've decided to make a career change into the world of technology. I'm currently learning to code online via Codecademy pursing a career path as a full stack developer. I believe that my educational background in engineering, years of leadership experience in a fast paced environment along with my problem solving skills and attention to detail will give me an advantage as I transition into this new career path. I'm very excited for this new venture and to overcome any challenges that may lie ahead as I embark on this journey.

WORK EXPERIENCE

GENERAL MANAGER

City, O' City/Watercourse Foods/Campus Lounge Denver, CO (Aug. 2015 - Sep. 2020)

ASSISTANT MANAGER

Native Foods Café, Denver, CO (Oct 2013 – Aug 2015)

HEAD SERVER

Joe's Bar on Weed St, Chicago, IL (Aug 2012 - Sep 2013)

NANNY/HOUSE MANAGER

Pamela Gould-Rashid, Wilmette, IL (Nov 2009 - Apr 2013)

MANUFACTURING ENGINEER

Caterpillar, Inc, Aurora, IL (Jan 2008 – Mar 2009)

ENGINEERING INTERN

Caterpillar, Inc. Aurora, IL (May 2005 – Dec 2007)

SKILLS

Leadership | Management | Problem Solving | Organization | Collaboration | Teamwork | Process Improvement | Punctuality | Operational Efficiency | Adaptability | Emotional Intelligence | Cultural Awareness | Building Relationships

EDUCATION

Northern Illinois University, DeKalb, IL Bachelor of Science in Mechanical Engineering Dec 2007

REFERENCES

Available upon request